<resources>
    <string name="app_name">FitnessUp</string>
    <string name="hint_email">Email</string>
    <string name="hint_phone">Phone</string>
    <string name="hint_confirm_password">Confirm Password</string>
    <string name="username_tx">username</string>
    <string name="forget_password_txt">Forget Password?</string>
    <string name="login_txt">Login</string>
    <string name="register_txt">REGISTER</string>
    <string name="register_page_txt">Register Page</string>
    <string name="enter_full_name_txt">Enter Full Name</string>
    <string name="user_name_txt">User Name</string>
    <string name="email_txt">Email</string>
    <string name="password">Password</string>
    <string name="your_fitness_app">Your Fitness App</string>
    <string name="forget_password_tx">Forget Password</string>
    <string name="enter_your_email_to_receive_otp">Enter your email to receive reset password link</string>
    <string name="enter_email">Enter Email</string>
    <string name="next_txtx">Next</string>
    <string name="fitnessapp_slogan">FitnessApp</string>
    <string name="open">open</string>
    <string name="close">close</string>
    <string name="home">Home</string>
    <string name="setting">Setting</string>
    <string name="title_activity_home">Home</string>
    <string name="navigation_drawer_open">Open navigation drawer</string>
    <string name="navigation_drawer_close">Close navigation drawer</string>
    <string name="nav_header_title">Android Studio</string>
    <string name="nav_header_subtitle">android.studio@android.com</string>
    <string name="nav_header_desc">Navigation header</string>
    <string name="action_settings">Settings</string>

    <string name="menu_home">Home</string>
    <string name="log_out">Log Out</string>
    <string name="title_activity_home_page">HomePage</string>
    <!-- TODO: Remove or change this placeholder text -->
    <string name="hello_blank_fragment">Hello blank fragment</string>
    <string name="user_id">ID</string>
    <string name="title_activity_home2">Home2</string>
    <string name="profile">Profile</string>
    <string name="email_login">Email</string>
    <string name="android_studio">Android Studio</string>
    <string name="share">Share</string>
    <string name="about">About</string>
    <string name="help_center">Help Center</string>
    <string name="others_txtx">Others</string>
    <string name="social">Social</string>
    <string name="bml_calculator">BML Calculator</string>
    <string name="press_for_more_info">Press Here For More Info</string>
    <string name="imperial_txt">Imperial</string>
    <string name="weight_metric">Weight in kg</string>
    <string name="height_metric">Height in m</string>
    <string name="weight_imperial">Weight in pounds</string>
    <string name="height_imperial">Height in inch</string>
    <string name="more_information">More information on Wikipedia</string>
    <string name="wikipedia_bmi_link">https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Body_mass_index</string>
    <string name="bmi_result">BMI: %s</string>
    <string name="bmi_cat_1">Very severely underweight</string>
    <string name="bmi_cat_2">Severely underweight</string>
    <string name="bmi_cat_3">Underweight</string>
    <string name="bmi_cat_4">Normal (healthy weight)</string>
    <string name="bmi_cat_5">Overweight</string>
    <string name="bmi_cat_6">Obese Class I (Moderately obese)</string>
    <string name="bmi_cat_7">Obese Class II (Severely obese)</string>
    <string name="bmi_cat_8">Obese Class III (Very severely obese)</string>
    <string name="bmi_cat_9">Obese Class IV (Morbidly Obese)</string>
    <string name="bmi_cat_10">Obese Class V (Super Obese)</string>
    <string name="bmi_cat_11">Obese Class VI (Hyper Obese)</string>
    <string name="imperial">Imperial</string>
    <string name="metric">Metric</string>
    <string name="default_unit">@string/metric</string>
    <string name="in_kgs">IN KGs</string>
    <string name="in_cms">IN CMs</string>
    <string name="calculate">Calculate</string>
    <string name="tips">Tips</string>
    <string name="title_activity_add_reminder">Create Reminder</string>
    <string name="title_activity_edit_reminder">Edit Reminder</string>
    <string name="add_reminder">Please Enter Your Reminder Note Here!</string>
    <string name="details">Other Information</string>
    <string name="date">Date</string>
    <string name="time">Time</string>
    <string name="repeat">Repeat</string>
    <string name="repeat_off">Off</string>
    <string name="repeat_no">Repetition Interval</string>
    <string name="repeat_type">Type of Repetitions</string>
    <string name="action_discard_reminder">Remove Your Reminder</string>
    <string name="action_save_reminder">Save Your Reminder</string>
    <string name="no_reminders">Please click on Float button to create a reminder</string>
    <string name="weight_loss">If you are reading this, it means that you concern about losing weight.
        Our application offers you a unique training methods of different workouts. Cardio full body and trouble zone oriented workouts will help you burn more calories in less time. To maintain a stable weight loss, take a closer look at your eating habits and make healthy choices. In this app, you will discover the important info about working out and everything connected with healthy living.</string>
    <string name="about_lose_weight">About Lose Weight</string>
    <string name="contact_us">Contact Us</string>
    <string name="title_activity_bottom_nav">MainActivity</string>
    <string name="title_home">Home</string>
    <string name="title_dashboard">Dashboard</string>
    <string name="title_notifications">Notifications</string>
    <string name="motivation">In order to achieve your weight loss goals faster, maintain your motivation hign. There are some adivces which will increase your level motivation. First, stick to the plan. It makes your workout more challeging when you follow a plan, gradually increase the workout intensity and review your stats and progress. Second, get an audio instructuion. It will help you to workout correctly and will stay motivated. Last but no least, manage your workout schedule. Develop a schedule, so that you can workout based on the scheduled.</string>
    <string name="waterandfood">Hydrate throughtout your day, not just after a workout.Get in the habit of sipping water continuously during the day. If you start your workout dehydrated, you won\'t get the maximum out of your workout, as water helps your body to exercise more efficiently. General guidelines are to drink 17 to 20 ounces of water 2 to 3 hours before exercising, another 8 ounces during your warm-up, 7 to 10 ounces every 10 to 20 minutes during exercise, and 8 ounces of water within 30 minutes after exercising.</string>
    <string name="workout">Strength training or crdio? Which is better? Although it\'s a reasonable question, there is no correct answer. Each exercise is different and achieves totally different result. Cardio improves your cardiovascular fitness and it is the main method of burning fat and losing weight. Strength training builds and strengthens your muscles to make you stronger and improve muscle definition. So whether you exercise for health reasons or just to look good, both types of exercise are important.</string>
    <string name="drinktoavoid">The calories that we drink dont make us feel full, so why consume them? Here are a few examples: a fancy coffee drink with milk and whipped cream can contain up to 800 calories, one glass of soda contained about 140 calories . You are now loaded with calories, and you ares till hungry. Additionally, due to the high sugar levels in most of such drinks, you will most likely overeat afterwards. So it it important to watch what you drink.</string>
    <string name="avoidfood">Try to avoid any over-processed foods-pastry, cheese and meat. Homemade baked goods and regular meat and cheese are fine on occasion, but processed food are packed with sugar and contained a lots of unhealthy ingredients that are harmful for your health. Soda and fancy coffee drinks can contain as many calories as a meal except that they wont fill you up.Most fast food prodcuts are to be avoided too, but we are sure that you know that. So, stay away from processed food and stay healthy.</string>
    <string name="sugar">Many adults eat much more sugar than necessary, so reducing added sugar intake is a healthful idea for most people. Some people may wish to take it a step further and cut sugar out of their diet entirely. The no-sugar diet has gained popularity as people continue to look for effective ways to live a healthful life or lose weight.</string>
    <string name="salt">We live in a society that measures and medicates. All the tools and technology and medicines deployed to maintain heart health are a help. However, heart disease remains the No. 1 killer in America. And high blood pressure, or hypertension, is a major contributor. Even so, heart disease is largely preventable, and much of that prevention lies in small steps that can make a big difference; diet is foremost among them. To lower your blood pressure, you need to reduce salt intake.</string>
    <string name="ttip">For new presentations, you’ll spend at least 10 hours outlining, researching, and creating your presentation for every seminar hour. Thus, a new eight-hour seminar will take 80 to 100 hours to create. So prepare it at least one month in advance, and practice it several times before presenting it. Always plan to speak for less time than you anticipate, so you can leave room in your program for spontaneous stories, unanticipated conversations, and unexpected questions.</string>
    <string name="gfp">Polyunsatured fats are essential fats, meaning that our bodies ned them to function properly. Among their primary functions are building cell membranes and the covering of nerves. Polyunsaturated fats are necessary for muscle movement and blood clotting. Polyunsaturated fats can help reduce bad cholesterol levels in your blood which can lower your risk of heart disease and stroke. They also provide nutrients to help develop and maintain your body’s cells. </string>
    <string name="protein">Protein is an organic compund that is made up of amino acids and is an essential part of any complex living organism. Most cells in out bodies are made up of protein, which we need to grow and to recover. Protein is also an important element of our muscle tissue, hair, immune system and it makes up essential hormones.Because we don’t store amino acids, our bodies make them in two different ways: either from scratch, or by modifying others. Nine amino acids—histidine, isoleucine, leucine, lysine, methionine, phenylalanine, threonine, tryptophan, and valine—known as the essential amino acids, must come from food.</string>
    <string name="good_fats_monounsaturated_fats">Good fats: monounsaturated fats</string>
    <string name="from_a_chemical_standpoint_monounsaturated_fats_are_simply_fat_molecules_that_have_one_unsaturated_carbon_bond_in_the_molecule_this_is_also_called_a_double_bond_oils_that_contain_monounsaturated_fats_are_typically_liquid_at_room_temperature_but_start_to_turn_solid_when_chilled_olive_oil_is_an_example_of_a_type_of_oil_that_contains_monounsaturated_fats">From a chemical standpoint, monounsaturated fats are simply fat molecules that have one unsaturated carbon bond in the molecule, this is also called a double bond. Oils that contain monounsaturated fats are typically liquid at room temperature but start to turn solid when chilled. Olive oil is an example of a type of oil that contains monounsaturated fats.</string>
    <string name="weight_myths">There is a lot of advice out there about food and weight loss, but let\'s take a critical approach. The first myth associated with weigth loss is about eating late in the day. The fact is you can eat any time if you eat healthy and count your calories. Overeating during the day is as likely to cause weight gain as in the evening. Another common myth is that carbs are abd for you. But the true is, you need carbs daily and need to be carefully select your carbs and avoid bad ones</string>
    <string name="bnm">If you stick to all weight lodd rules that we listed, you will see result. However, there is additional advice better than mentioning. If you think you do everything necessary but your weigth is still the same and you dont see any improvement in how you loo, you might be doing something wrong. For example, you may not be counting all calories. Some believe that nly bg meals need to be counted. However, snacks and drink also have calories and count towards your daily calorie allowance. Do not forget to include them in your food journal and you may find that you exceed your daily limit.Rememebr, eat wise and stay healthy.</string>
    <string name="cc">Some experts believe that correct calorie counting is an important step in reaching healthy weight loss goals. While the process may seem very simple, there are a number of common mistakes that can derail success. Use this list of calorie counting tips to make sure you end up with the right numbers to create weight loss success. Most women end up with a number around 1,200 calories per day to lose weight. Men often end up with a number close to 1,800 calories per day to lose weight.</string>
    <string name="veg">Vegetables are low in fat and calories as well as are contaiend abundant vitamins, minerals, antioxidants and fiber. It is necessary to eat about 5 servings of vegetables daily, preferably a variety of types and colors. In all cases- fresh raw vegetables are the most usefull as they lose a significant amount of their nutrition value in the cooking process. As more, dried and frozen vegetables are a good choice when certain vegetables are out of season.</string>
    <string name="vitamin">Vitamins and minerals are essential nutrients because they perform hundreds of roles in the body. There is a fine line between getting enough of these nutrients (which is healthy) and getting too much (which can end up harming you). Eating a healthy diet remains the best way to get sufficient amounts of the vitamins and minerals you need. Every day, your body produces skin, muscle, and bone. It churns out rich red blood that carries nutrients and oxygen to remote outposts, and it sends nerve signals skipping along thousands of miles of brain and body pathways.</string>
    <string name="pre_workout">This Pre workout execrise is to let you easy to stretches even help those who don’t workout: Don’t consider them a real workout, but instead think about stretching regularly as a passive form of stress relief, like taking a bath or getting a massage. </string>
    <string name="steps3_ac">3. Continue for 15 circles, then reverse directions and complete 15 rotations in the opposite direction.</string>
    <string name="steps2_ac">2. Slowly rotate your shoulders and arms to make forward circles about 1 foot in diameter.</string>
    <string name="step1_ac">1. Stand with your feet shoulder-width apart. Extend both arms out straight to your sides to form a T with your body.</string>
    <string name="plank_abs">1. Lay on your stomach and push yourself off the ground</string>
    <string name="plank_abs2">2. Rest your weight on your forearms and keep the body straight from heel to head.</string>
    <string name="plank_abs3">3. Hold the position for the length of the exercise.</string>
    <string name="superman1">1. Lay face down on a mat or flat surface, with arms outstretched.</string>
    <string name="superman2">2. Keep your hands and arms straight throughout the exercise.</string>
    <string name="superman3">3. Raise your hand and legs 4-5 inches off the ground.</string>
    <string name="superman4">4. Hold for 5 seconds, then return to starting position.</string>
    <string name="asstep1">1. Stand upright and clasp your hands together over your head</string>
    <string name="assstep2">2. Stop forcing when your arms reach the limit</string>
    <string name="assteps3">3. Stand straight and do not lean forward or backward.</string>
    <string name="pushup_step11">1. Get down on all fours, placing your hands slightly wider than your shoulders.</string>
    <string name="pushup22">2. Straighten your arms and legs.</string>
    <string name="pushup33">3. Lower your body until your chest nearly touches the floor.</string>
    <string name="triceps1">1. Place your hands shoulder-width apart on the furniture you’re propping yourself up on.</string>
    <string name="tripces2">2. Shift your pelvis and bottom forward so there’s a 3- to 6-inch gap between your back and the object.</string>
    <string name="triceps3">3. Bend your legs in a 90-degree angle with your feet planted firmly on the ground, or extend them out in front of you (but don’t lock your knees).</string>
    <string name="triceps44">4. Slowly lower your body down and back up, focusing on engaging your triceps.</string>
    <string name="wpu_step1">1. Start in plank position with your hands wider than your shoulders.</string>
    <string name="wpu_step2">2. Face your fingers forward or slightly to the outside.</string>
    <string name="wpu_step3">3. Slowly bend your elbows out to the side as you lower your body toward the floor.</string>
    <string name="wpu_step4">4. Pause when your chest is just below your elbows.</string>
    <string name="wpu_step5">5. Engage your core as you press into your hands to lift your body back to the starting position.</string>
    <string name="aspu_steps1">1. Start facing your anchor, holding one battle rope in each hand, feet just wider than shoulder-width apart, knees slightly bent.</string>
    <string name="aspu_steps2">2. Begin side shuffling to the right as you lift the right hand and rope up to shoulder level, while simultaneously lowering the left hand and rope down to hip level.</string>
    <string name="aspu_steps3">3. Alternate arms quickly as you side shuffle 5 steps to the right. Without stopping your arms, change direction and side shuffle to the left for 5 steps.</string>
    <string name="bicycle_steps1">1. Start lying flat on your back, legs fully extended, and both hands behind the head.</string>
    <string name="bicycle_steps4">4. Make sure to keep the leg that isn’t bending fully extended and low to the floor to get the best engagement</string>
    <string name="bicycle_steps3">3. Bring your right knee toward your chest and rotate your shoulders to move the left elbow to toward the right knee.</string>
    <string name="bicycle_steps2">2. From here, bring both hands behind the head and raise the shoulders off the floor.</string>
    <string name="dpu_stepss1">1. Get in a press-up position and place your hands together so your index fingers and thumbs form a diamond</string>
    <string name="dpu_stepss2">2. Keep your back straight as you lower until your chest almost touches the floor then push back up to the start position.</string>
    <string name="opi_stepss1">1. Stand in a push-up position with your feet out wide.</string>
    <string name="opi_stepss2">2. Descend into a push-up until the same side pec is just off the floor. Keeping your opposite side shoulder slightly elevated if necessary for better balance.</string>
    <string name="opi_stepss3">3. Repeat for the recommended number of reps and switch to the opposite side.</string>
    <string name="incline_steps1">1. Place your hands on the edge of the bench just slightly wider than shoulder width.</string>
    <string name="incline_steps2">2. Bend your elbows to slowly lower your chest to the edge of the bench while inhaling. Keep your body straight and rigid throughout the movement.</string>
    <string name="iincline_steps3">3. Push your body away from the bench until your elbows are extended, but not locked. Exhale as you push up.</string>
    <string name="decline_steps1">1. Kneel down with your back to the bench. Put your hands on the floor, shoulders over your wrists and elbows at 45 degrees. Place your feet on top of the bench.</string>
    <string name="decline_steps2">2. Brace your core, glutes, and quads. Bend your elbows and lower your chest to the floor, keeping your back and neck straight.</string>
    <string name="decline_steps3">3. Push into the floor to return to starting position, extending your elbows.</string>
    <string name="squat_steps1">1. Stand with your feet about shoulder-width apart and slightly turned out with your weight in your heels.</string>
    <string name="squat_steps2">2. Hinge forward at your hips and sit your butt back into a squat. Bend your knees until your thighs are parallel to the ground.</string>
    <string name="squat_steps3">3. Drive through your heels to stand back up straight. Squeeze your butt and keep your core tight as you stand.</string>
    <string name="sj_steps1">1. Stand with your feet slightly wider than hip-width apart.</string>
    <string name="sj_steps2">2. Hinge forward at your hips and sit your butt back into a squat. Bend your knees until your thighs are parallel to the ground.</string>
    <string name="sj_steps3">3.Jump up into the air as high as you can and straighten out your legs. Swing your arms down by your sides for momentum, and keep your back straight and chest lifted.</string>
    <string name="sidelunge_stepss1">1. Stand with your feet hip-width apart.</string>
    <string name="sidelunges_stepss2">2. Take a big step out to your right. Bend your right knee and push your butt back, keeping your left leg straight. Keep your chest lifted and core tight.</string>
    <string name="sidelunge_steps3">3. Repeat on the other side.</string>
    <string name="ps_stepss1">1. Lift your left leg a few inches and extend it forward, foot flexed.</string>
    <string name="ps_stepss2">2. Bend your right knee, hinge forward at the hips, and sit back into a squat while lifting your left leg to hip height. Extend your arms out for balance.</string>
    <string name="ps_stepss3">3. Try to bend your knee to 90 degrees if you can and push through your right heel to straighten your leg and return to start.</string>
    <string name="lunge_stepss1">1. Take a split stance so when you lower yourself into the lunge, both knees are bent at 90°.</string>
    <string name="lunge_stepss3">3. Your trailing left leg should be used to support and balance you as you drive upwards through the heel of your right (forward) leg.</string>
    <string name="lunges_step2">2. If your right leg is forward, place most of the load through this foot, aiming to keep it firm and flat against the floor at all times.</string>
    <string name="calfr_steps2">2.Stand tall with your abdominals pulled in, the balls of your feet firmly planted on the step, and your heels hanging over the edge.</string>
    <string name="calfr_stepss1">1. Stand on the edge of a step.</string>
    <string name="calf_steps3">3. Raise your heels a few inches above the edge of the step so that you’re on your tiptoes.</string>
    <string name="calrf_steps4">4. Hold the position for a moment, and then lower your heels below the platform, feeling a stretch in your calf muscles.</string>
    <string name="donkey_stepss1">1. Assume the starting position on all fours: knees hip-width apart, hands under your shoulders, neck and spine neutral.</string>
    <string name="donkey_stepss2">2. Bracing your core, begin to lift your right leg, knee staying bent, foot staying flat, and hinging at the hip.</string>
    <string name="donkey_stepss3">3. Use your glute to press your foot directly toward the ceiling and squeeze at the top. Ensure your pelvis and working hip stay pointed toward the ground.</string>
    <string name="donkey_stepss4">4. Return to the starting position.</string>
    <string name="bk_stepss1">1. Lying on the back, fully extend the legs. The entire body should be parallel to the ground.</string>
    <string name="bk_stepss2">2. Place arms above the head or off to the side for added stability.</string>
    <string name="bk_stepss3">3. Slowly bring the left leg toward the chest, bending at the knee as it comes to the chest. Bring it as close as it will go.</string>
    <string name="bk_stepss4">4. With the left leg is at the chest, bring the right leg, bending at the knee, toward the chest while at the same time.</string>
    <string name="crunches_stepss1">1. Lie down on your back. Plant your feet on the floor, hip-width apart. Bend your knees and place your arms across your chest. Contract your abs and inhale.</string>
    <string name="crunches_stepss2">2. Exhale and lift your upper body, keeping your head and neck relaxed.</string>
    <string name="crunches_stepss3">3. Inhale and return to the starting position.</string>
    <string name="jj_stepss1">1. Stand upright with your legs together, arms at your sides</string>
    <string name="jj_stepss2">2. Bend your knees slightly, and jump into the air.</string>
    <string name="jj_stepss3">3. As you jump, spread your legs to be about shoulder-width apart. Stretch your arms out and over your head.</string>
    <string name="jj_stepss4">4. Jump back to starting position.</string>
    <string name="leg_stepss1">1. Lie on your back and raise your legs until they’re perpendicular to the floor. Keep them straight and squeezed together.</string>
    <string name="leg_stepss2">2. Use your hands to support your neck by gently placing your palms on the back of your head.</string>
    <string name="leg_stepss3">3. Engage your abdominal muscles and lift your shoulders and upper back off the floor. Think about lifting your chest to the sky instead of rounding your shoulders.</string>
    <string name="leg_stepss4">4. Hold the crunch for one second and slowly lower the upper body to the starting position, and repeat.</string>
    <string name="mc_stepss1">1. Get into a plank position, making sure to distribute your weight evenly between your hands and your toes.</string>
    <string name="mc_stepss2">2. Check your form—your hands should be about shoulder-width apart, back flat, abs engaged, and head in alignment.</string>
    <string name="mc_stepss3">3. Pull your right knee into your chest as far as you can.</string>
    <string name="mc_stepss4">4. Switch legs, pulling one knee out and bringing the other knee in.</string>
    <string name="mc_stepss5">5. Keep your hips down, run your knees in and out as far and as fast as you can.</string>
    <string name="rt_stepss1">1. Sit on your sit bones as you lift your feet from the floor, keeping your knees bent.</string>
    <string name="rt_stepss2">2. Elongate and straighten your spine at a 45-degree angle from the floor, creating a V shape with your torso and thighs.</string>
    <string name="rt_stepss3">3. Reach your arms straight out in front, interlacing your fingers or clasping your hands together.</string>
    <string name="rt_stepss4">4. Use your abdominals to twist to the right, then back to center, and then to the left.</string>
    <string name="spl_stepss1">1. Start on your side with your feet together and one forearm directly below your shoulder.</string>
    <string name="spl_stepps2">2. Contract your core and raise your hips until your body is in a straight line from head to feet.</string>
    <string name="spl_stepss3">3. Hold the position without letting your hips drop for the allotted time for each set, then repeat on the other side.</string>
    <string name="reminder_setting">Settings</string>
    <string name="SendText">Send us a message if you have enquiry about the application</string>
    <string name="h1ingredients">1 tbsp tamari -1 tsp medium curry powder -¼ tsp ground cumin -1 garlic clove, finely grated -1 tsp clear honey -2 skinless chicken breast fillets (or use turkey breast) -1 tbsp crunchy peanut butter -1 tbsp sweet chilli sauce -1 tbsp lime juice -a little sunflower oi; -2 Little Gem lettuces hearts, cut into wedges -¼ cucumber, halved and sliced</string>
    <string name="instructionh1">Pour the tamari into a large dish and stir in the curry powder, cumin, garlic and honey. Mix well. Slice the chicken breasts in half horizontally to make 4 fillets in total, then add to the marinade and mix well to coat. Set aside in the fridge for at least 1 hr. Meanwhile, mix the peanut butter with the chilli sauce, lime juice, and 1 tbsp water to make a spoonable sauce. When ready to cook the chicken, wipe a large non-stick frying pan with a little oil. Add the chicken and cook, covered with a lid, for 5-6 mins on a medium heat, until cooked but still moist. Set aside, covered, to rest for a few mins. While the chicken rests, toss the lettuce wedges with the cucumber, shallot, coriander and pomegranate, and pile onto plates. Spoon over a little sauce. Slice the chicken, pile on top of the salad and spoon over the remaining sauce. Eat while the chicken is still warm.</string>
    <string name="h2ingredietns">6 skinless chicken breasts | -2 tbsp olive oil | -1⁄2 tbsp balsamic vinegar | -140g bag rocket | -25g parmesan lemon wedges | -2 garlic cloves | -3 rosemary leaves finely chopped, leaves finely chopped | -6age | -1 lemon and juice of ½ | -3 tbsp olive oil</string>
    <string name="h3instruction">Put the onion, garlic, ginger and tomatoes in a food processor or blender and whizz to a purée. Heat oil in a large pan. Add the spices, fry for a few secs and add purée and yeast extract. Bubble together for 2 mins, then add lentils and coconut cream. Cook until lentils are tender, then add the broccoli and cook for 4 mins. Stir in chickpeas and spinach, squeeze over lemon and swirl through sesame and cashew mixture. Serve with brown rice, if you like.</string>
    <string name="h4instruction">Drain the pineapple, reserving the juice. If in rings, chop into chunks. Mix with the chicken, onion, leaves, coriander and tomatoes, and divide between 2 containers if taking as lunch. For the dressing, whisk 2 tbsp of the pineapple juice, the red chilli, vinegar and sweet chilli sauce with some seasoning in a small jam jar or lidded container, and toss this through the salad before serving.</string>
    <string name="h4ingredietns">227g can pineapple in juice about 140g pack cooked, sliced chicken breast (sweet chilli, hot and spice or BBQ work well) | 1 small red onion, halved and thinly sliced | 90g bag mixed leaf small bunch coriander, leaves picked handful cherry tomatoes, halved | 1 red chilli, deseeded and chopped | 2 tbsp white wine vinegar | 1 tbsp sweet chilli sauce</string>
    <string name="h5instructions">Make the sauce and marinade. In a small bowl, whisk together the soy, honey, garlic and mirin and set aside. Cut out some squares of foil. Using scissors, cut out 4 squares of foil, each about 30cm square. Brush each piece of foil with a little oil and bring the edges of the foil up a little. Fill your parcels. Place a couple of broccoli stems on each one, then sit a salmon fillet on top and scatter over the ginger. Spoon over the sauce. Spoon the sauce over each salmon fillet and drizzle with a little sesame oil, if you like. Close the parcels. Fold over the edges of the foil together to seal and place the parcels on a baking sheet. Can be prepared up to 1 day ahead. Cook the parcels. Heat oven to 200C/180C fan/gas 6. Get your child to place the parcels in the oven for 15-20 mins, but ensure an adult removes them, then leave to stand for a few mins. Serve each parcel on a plate and let each person open it themselves. Serve with spring onions and sesame seeds for scattering over, and some rice on the side.</string>
    <string name="h2instruction">Place each chicken breast between 2 sheets of cling film or baking parchment. Use a meat mallet or rolling pin to bash each piece of chicken – flatten out to an even layer about 0.5cm thick. Transfer to a dish. To make the marinade, crush the garlic with a good pinch of salt using a pestle and mortar. Add the rosemary and sage, and give everything a good pounding. Stir through the lemon zest and juice, olive oil and some ground black pepper. Pour the marinade over the chicken, ensuring that it’s well coated. Cover and chill for at least 2 hrs. Heat the barbecue. Once the flames have died down, spread the coals out to an even layer. Cook the chicken for 1-2 mins each side. Transfer to a board and leave to rest for a few mins. Meanwhile, pour the oil and balsamic vinegar into a large bowl. Add the rocket and some seasoning. Toss together, then shave over the Parmesan. Serve the salad with the chicken, with lemon wedges to squeeze over.</string>
    <string name="h3instructions">1 onion ,chopped | 2 garlic cloves, chopped | 3cm/1¼ in piece ginger, grated | 6 ripe tomatoes |½ tbsp oil | 1 tsp ground cumin | 2 tsp ground coriander | 1 tsp turmeric pinch chilli flakes | 1 tsp yeast extract (we used Marmite) | 4 tbsp red lentils | 6 tbsp coconut cream | 1 head of broccoli, broken into small florets | 400g can chickpeas, drained | 100g bag baby spinach leaves | 1 lemon, halved | 1 tbsp toasted sesame seed | 1 tbsp chopped cashew, to mix with the sesame seeds</string>
    <string name="h5ingredients">2 tbsp low-salt soy sauce | 1 tbsp clear honey | 1 garlic clove, finely chopped | 1 tbsp mirin (optional) a little sunflower oil | 300g Tenderstem broccoli |4 x 100g salmon fillets | 1 small piece of ginger, cut into matchsticks a little sesame oil (optional) sliced spring onions, toasted sesame seeds and cooked rice, to serve</string>
    <string name="h6instruction">Heat the oil in a heavy-based frying pan. Stir in the onions, pepper and chillies. Cook until they begin to soften. Add the tomatoes and sugar, mixing well. Cook until the liquid has reduced, season.Using a wooden spoon, create 4 pockets in the tomato mixture and crack the eggs into them. Cover the pan and cook the eggs over a low heat until just set.Beat the yogurt with the garlic and season. Sprinkle the menemen with parsley and serve from the frying pan with a dollop of the garlic-flavoured yogurt.</string>
    <string name="h6ingredients">2 tbsp olive oil | 2 onions, sliced | 1 red or green pepper, halved deseeded and sliced | 1-2 red chillies, deseeded and sliced | 400g can chopped tomatoes | 1-2 tsp caster sugar | 4 eggs small bunch parsley, roughly chopped | 6 tbsp thick, creamy yogurt yogurtYogurt yog-ert</string>
    <string name="character_counter_pattern" translatable="false">%1$d/%2$d</string>
    <!-- Content description for the character counter text [CHAR LIMIT=NONE] -->
    <string name="character_counter_content_description">Characters entered %1$d of %2$d</string>
    <!-- Content description for the character counter text when it has overflowed [CHAR LIMIT=NONE] -->
    <string name="character_counter_overflowed_content_description">Character limit exceeded %1$d of %2$d</string>
    <!-- Content description for the password visibility toggle button. [CHAR LIMIT=NONE] -->
    <string name="password_toggle_content_description">Show password</string>
    <!-- Content description for the clear text button end icon. [CHAR LIMIT=NONE] -->
    <string name="clear_text_end_icon_content_description">Clear text</string>
    <!-- Content description for the exposed dropdown menu button. [CHAR LIMIT=NONE] -->
    <string name="exposed_dropdown_menu_content_description">Show dropdown menu</string>
    <!-- Content description for the error icon. [CHAR LIMIT=NONE] -->
    <string name="error_icon_content_description">Error</string>
    <string name="title_activity_bml">BmlActivity</string>
    <!-- Strings used for fragments for navigation -->
    <string name="first_fragment_label">First Fragment</string>
    <string name="second_fragment_label">Second Fragment</string>
    <string name="next">Next</string>
    <string name="previous">Previous</string>

    <string name="hello_first_fragment">Hello first fragment</string>
    <string name="hello_second_fragment">Hello second fragment. Arg: %1$s</string>

</resources>
